Guide to the J. Arthur (Jesse Arthur) Younger Papers, 1951-1968
Department of Special Collections
- COMMUNICATIONS, FCC
  - 1957 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - 1963 - 1964 (Box 7, Folder 31, Folder 32, Folder 30, Folder 33)
- COMMUNISM, GENERAL, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- COMPENSATION
  - 1955 - 1962 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 1963 - 1964 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - 1965 - 1966 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- CONGRESS, GENERAL
  - 1963 - 1964 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - 1965 - 1966 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Congress, House of Rep., Fiscal Org. Comm. (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Congress, House of Rep., Joint Comm. on Econ. (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Congress, House of Rep., Joint Comm. on Org. of Congress (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Congress, House of Rep., Rules Comm. (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Congress, House of Rep., Unamerican Activities Comm. (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Congressional pages, residence (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Congressional payroll (Box 4, Folder 33)
- CONGRESSIONAL RECORD
  - 1959 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Younger remarks, 1963(1) (Box 8, Folder 8)
    * see following 30 pp. for demized list
  - Younger remarks, 1963(2) (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Younger remarks, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Younger remarks, 1965(1) (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Younger remarks, 1965(2) (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Younger remarks, 1966(1) (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Younger remarks, 1966(2) (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Younger remarks, 1966(3) (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Younger remarks, 1967(1) (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Younger remarks, 1967(2) (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Congressional Reorganization (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Congressional Stationery Allowance (Box 4, Folder 34)
- CONNALLY RESERVATION (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Connelly, John H. (1903 -); Airline exec. (Box 6, Folder 18)
- CONSTRUCTION ON FILLED LAND (Box 8, Folder 19)
- GOVT. CONTRACTS, GENERAL
  - 1963 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - 1964 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - 1965 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - 1966 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Conway, John T. () (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Cooley, Gerald (Private bill) (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Coon, Sam () (Box 15, Folder 12, Box 21, Folder 6)
- Cootes, Merritt N. (); Fgn. Serv. Ofcl. (Box 19, Folder 24, Box 20, Folder 4)
- COPYRIGHTS & PATENTS, 1964 - 1965 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Corbett, Robert J. (1905 -); Cong., 29th & 30th Pa. (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Costenzo, Joseph B. () (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Cothram, James W. (1915 -); Lawyer (Box 22, Folder 22)
- COYOTE POINT PROJECT, 1954 - 1963 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Crafts, James F. (1899 -); Insurance exec. (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Cramer, William C. (1922 -); Cong., 1st Fla. (Box 15, Folder 9, Folder 12)
- Crandall, Henry W. (1898 -); Army officer (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Cranston, Alan () (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Cretella, Albert W. () (Box 15, Folder 12)
- CRIMES AND OFFENSES, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Crumpacher, Shepard J. (1917 -); Cong., 3rd Ind. (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Cruz, Dalisay (Private bill) (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Cunningham, Glenn (1912 -); Cong., 2nd Neb. (Box 14, Folder 3, Box 15, Folder 6)
- Curtis, Carl T. (1905 -); U. S. Sen., Neb. (Box 15, Folder 7, Box 19, Folder 1)
- Curtis, Lawrence (1893 -); Cong., 10th Mass. (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Curtis, Thomas B. (1911 -); Cong., 2nd Mo. (Box 15, Folder 12)
- CUSTOMS, GENERAL
  - 1963 - 1964 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - 1965 - 1966 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Czech claims (Box 3, Folder 13, Folder 16, Folder 32, Box 4, Folder 12)
- Dague, Paul B. (1898 -); Cong., 9th Pa. (Box 3, Folder 11, Box 13, Folder 7, Box 15, Folder 12)
- Davidson, J. F. () (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Dawson, William L. (1886 -); Cong., 1st Ill. (Box 4, Folder 26, Box 15, Folder 12, Folder 28)
- DEFENSE
  - 1953 - 1956 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - 1957 - 1958 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - 1963 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - 1964 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - 1965 - 1966 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Defense Materials Movement (Box 4, Folder 11)
- de Forest, Lee (1873 -); Inventor (Box 20, Folder 29)
- Dembling, Paul G. () (Box 5, Folder 35, Box 7, Folder 30)
- Demetrakopoulos, Thalia (Private bill) (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Dennison, David M. (1900 -); Theoretical physicist (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Dept. of ----, see under name, dept. of
- Dept. of Labor, Bureau of Employee's Compensation (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Derounian, Steven B. (1918 -); Cong., 2nd N. Y. (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Devereux, James P. S. (1903 -); Cong., 2nd Md.
- Dickerson, Nancy H. (); News Correspondent (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Dickinson, William L. () (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Diggins, John R. Jr. () (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Dillon, Thomas P. (1882 -); Fgn. serv. officer (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Dinkespiel, John Walton () (Box 2, Folder 2, Folder 3, Box 14, Folder 12, Box 16, Folder 9)
- Dirksen, Everett McKinley (1896 -); U. S. Sen. (Box 15, Folder 10)
- DISARMAMENT, GENERAL
  - 1963 - 1964 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - 1965 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- DISASTER AREAS, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- DISTRICT OF COLUMBIA, GENERAL, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Dixon, Henry Aldous (1890 -); Cong., 1st Utah (Box 4, Folder 28, Box 15, Folder 12)
- Dixon, Paul Rand (1913 -); Govt. official (Box 9, Folder 33, Box 13, Folder 1)
- Doerfer, John C. (1904 -); Chairman of FCC (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Dolliver, James I. (1894 -); Cong., 6th Iowa (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Dolwig, Richard J. () (Box 2, Folder 1, Box 6, Folder 5, Box 11, Folder 24, Box 19, Folder 27, Box 20, Folder 19, Folder 30)
- Donaho, Glynn R. (1905 -); Naval officer (Box 19, Folder 28)
- Donaldson, Allyn C. (1898 -); Govt. official (Box 19, Folder 24)
- Dorfman, Benjamin () (Box 20, Folder 19)
- DONATIONS, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Dorn, Francis E. (1911 -); Cong., 12th N. Y. (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Doub, George Cochran (1902 -); Govt. official (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Douglas, Donald W. (1892 -); Aircraft mfr. (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Douglas, James H. (1899 -); Govt. Official (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Doulens, Roger B. () (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Driscoll, James D. () (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Driver, William J. () (Box 8, Folder 23, Box 14, Folder 5)
- Drumright, Everett F. (1906 -); Fgn. Serv. officer (Box 5, Folder 2, Box 20, Folder 1, Folder 3)
- Du Bridge, Lee A. (1901 -); Physicist (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Duncan, John, J () (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Du Planty, Regine () (Box 3, Folder 15, Box 5, Folder 22)
- Durfee, James R. (1897 -); Govt. Official (Box 2, Folder 3, Folder 35, Box 3, Folder 17, Box 6, Folder 18, Folder 19, Folder 24)
- Durovic, Steven () (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Dutton, Frederick G. (1923 -); Spec. Asst. to Pres. (Box 10, Folder 13, Box 11, Folder 23, Folder 25, Box 14, Folder 12, Box 19, Folder 24)
- Du Val, Clive L. () (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Dykeman, Carl (Private bill) (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Earthquake, Alaskan Good Friday (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Easley, Bruce (1906 -); Army officer (Box 19, Folder 28)
- Eckert, William D. (1909 -); Air Force officer (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Eckler, A. Ross (1901 -); Govt. official (Box 6, Folder 15)
- ECONOMY, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Edmondson, Edward (1919 -); Cong., 2nd Okla. (Box 13, Folder 7)
- EDUCATION, GENERAL
  - 1963 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - 1965 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Edwards, Norman B. () (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Eisenhower, Dwight David (carbon) (1890 - 1969); Pres. of the U. S. (Box 5, Folder 27)
- ELECTION RETURNS, STATISTICS (Box 9, Folder 19)
- ELECTORAL COLLEGE (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Ellsworth, Harris () (Box 2, Folder 2, Box 7, Folder 9, Box 15, Folder 12)
- Ellsworth, Robert F. (1926 -); Cong., 2nd Kansas (Box 15, Folder 7)
- EMPLOYMENT
  - General, 1963 - 1966 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Summer, 1966 - 1967 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Endicott, Kenneth M. (1916 -); U.S.P.H.S. physician (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Engle, Clair (1911 -); U.S. Sen. (Box 13, Folder 6, Box 15, Folder 13, Box 18, Folder 2)
- Equal Time (FCC Act) (Box 4, Folder 1, Box 7, Folder 31)
- Erickson, Edgar C. (1896 -); Army officer (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Ernst, Roger (1914 -); Govt. Official
- ESTATES (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Evans, Roy T. (1911 -); Army officer (Box 4, Folder 20)
- EXPORTS, 1963 - 1966 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Fahy, Edward J. () (Box 8, Folder 23)
- FAIRS (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Farm subsidies (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Farrell, R. F. () (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Farrington, Elizabeth R. (1898 -); Newspaper Publ. Cong. (Box 13, Folder 6, Box 15, Folder 12)
- FAA Act Amdmt. (Box 4, Folder 21)
- FEDERAL AVIATION ACT, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- FEDERAL AVIATION AGENCY
  - 1963 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - 1965 - 1966 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- FBI, GENERAL (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Federal Communication Commission (Box 7, Folder 29, Folder 28, Folder 30, Folder 31, Folder 32)
- FEDERAL HOUSING ADMINISTRATION, CORRES.
  - 1955 - 1956 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - 1957 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- FEDERAL POWER COMMISSION, 1955 - 1966 (Box 9, Folder 32)
- FEDERAL TRADE COMMISION
  - 1955 - 1964 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - 1965 - 1966 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Misc. (Box 20, Folder 25)
- Fenton, Ivor D. (); Cong., 12th Pa. (Box 14, Folder 23, Box 15, Folder 12)
- FIELD OFFICE MEMOS
  - 1957 - 1958(from) (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - 1957 - 1958(to) (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - 1958 - 1959(from) (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - 1958 - 1960(from) (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - 1959 - 1960(to) (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Fine, Sidney H. (1906 -); Govt. Official (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Firth, Gordon R. () (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Fisheries (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Fisnucane, Charles C. (1905 -); Govt. official (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Fisnucane, Thomas G. (1898 -); Lawyer (Box 3, Folder 8)
- FITZGERALD, JOHN L. (1963 - 1964) (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - 1965 - 1966 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- FLAGS, GENERAL
  - 1963 - 1964 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - 1965 - 1966 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Floete, Franklin G. (1889 -); Govt. Official (Box 13, Folder 22, Box 14, Folder 7)
- FLOOD CONTROL (Box 3, Folder 20, Folder 21, Box 10, Folder 7)
- FLOWER GROWERS, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- FLUORIDATION
  - 1963 - 1964 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Misc. (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Flower shippers (Box 2, Folder 35, Folder 36, Box 3, Folder 17)
- Flues, A. Gilmore (1903 -); Govt. official (Box 4, Folder 22, Box 20, Folder 29, Folder 30)
- Fogarty, John E. (1913 -); Cong. (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Fogler, Raymond H. (1892 -); Corp. exec. (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Foley, Eugene P () (Box 19, Folder 1, Folder 8)
- FOOD AND DRUG, GENERAL
  - 1963 - 1964 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - 1965 - 1966 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Ford, Gerald R. (1913 -); Cong., 5th Mich. (Box 7, Folder 20, Box 15, Folder 6, Folder 12, Folder 22, Box 22, Folder 28)
- Ford, Henry II (1917 -); Auto mfr. (Box 22, Folder 26)
- Ford, Walter C. (1903 -); Naval officer (Box 7, Folder 16)
- FOREIGN AFFAIRS
  - General, 1959 - 1960 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - General, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Rhodesia, Jan., 1967 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Rhodesia, Feb., 1967 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Rhodesia, March & April, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Rhodesia, May & July, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- FOREIGN CLAIMS SETTLEMENT COMM., CORRES., 1955 - 1956 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- FOREIGN CLAIMS SETTLEMENT COMM., MISC. (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Foreign Service Academy (Box 4, Folder 13)
- FOREIGN TRADE, GENERAL
  - 1963 - 1964 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - 1965 - 1966 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Foster, T. Jack Jr. () (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Foster, William C. (1897 -); Corp. exec. (Box 9, Folder 11)
- FOUNDATIONS, 1963 - 1966 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Freas, Howard G. (1900 -); Govt. official (Box 1, Folder 9, Box 4, Folder 27)
- Freeman, Orville (1918 -); Gov. of Minn.
- Freitas, Jorge (Private bill) (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Frelinghuysen, Peter, Jr. (1916 -); Cong., 5th N. J. (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Frew, Arnold () (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Friedel, Samuel N. (1898 -); Cong., 7th Md. (Folder 4, Folder 9, Box 4, Folder 33)
- Fu, William (Private bill)
- Fujii, Katsutoshi (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Fulton, James Grove (1903 -); Cong., 27th Pa. (Box 14, Folder 31)
- Gadsby, Edward N. (1900 -); Govt. official (Box 18, Folder 22)
- Gamble, Ralph A. () (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Gannon, Donald Huie () (Box 20, Folder 24, Box 22, Folder 28)
- Garner, Robert L. (1894 -); International banker (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Gaspard, Jerome T. (1907 -); Fgn. Serv. officer (Box 19, Folder 24, Box 20, Folder 4)
- Geerken, Forrest K. (1908 -); Fgn Serv. officer (Box 20, Folder 1)
- GENEALOGY (Box 10, Folder 23)
- GENERAL ACCOUNTING OFFICE, 1955 - 1965 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- General Agreement on Trade & Tariffs (GATT) (Box 20, Folder 16)
- GENERAL SERVICES ADMINISTRATION
  - 1955 - 1956 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - 1957 - 1961 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - 1962 - 1966 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Gibson, Philip S. (); Chief Justice, Supreme Court of Cal. (Box 22, Folder 22)
- GIFFORD, GERALDIDINE, 1963 - 1966 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Gifford, Selene () (Box k2, Folder 3)
- Gilliss, C. M. () (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Gilstrap, Samuel P. (1907 -); Fgn. Serv. officer (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Gleason, James P. (1921 -); Lawyer, govt. official (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Gleason, John S. Jr. (1915 -); Nat. Commander, Am. Legion (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Goff, Abe McGregor (1899 -); Govt. official (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Golden Gate National Cemetery (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Goodell, Charles E. (1926 -); Cong., 43rd N. Y. (Box 13, Folder 7, Box 22, Folder 9)
- Goodwin, Robert C. (1898 -); Dean, Tex. Tech. College (Box 19, Folder 22)
- Gordon, Seth (1890 -); Wildlife Cons. writer (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Gordon, Walter A. (1894 -); District judge (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Gould, Charles L. (1909 -); Newspaper exec. (Box 15, Folder 2)
- GOVERNMENT, GENERAL
  - 1963 - 1965 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- GOVERNMENT PRINTING OFFICE, 1955 - 1964 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Graham, Angus (Lord) (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Granucci, Cardone (Private bill) (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Greene, Wallace M. Jr. (1907 -); Marine corps officer (Box 13, Folder 31)
- Greenwalt, Crawford H. (1902 -); Business exec. (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Grieves, Howard C. (1910 -); Statistician (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Gronouski, John A. () (Box 16, Folder 5, Folder 6)
- Gross, H. R. (1899 -); Cong., 3rd Iowa (Box 15, Folder 9, Folder 12)
- Grover, Wayne C. (1906 -); U. S. archivist (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Grover, James R. Jr. () (Box 14, Folder 31)
- Gruening, Ernest (1887 -); U. S. Senator (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Gubser, Charles S. (1916 -); Cong., 10th Cal. (Box 3, Folder 2, Box 5, Folder 31, Box 15, Folder 3, Folder 12)
- Gunn, Frank L. () (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Gwynne, John W. () (Box 20, Folder 25)
- Hagen, Harlan (1914 -); Congressman (Box 4, Folder 2, Box 6, Folder 7, Box 15, Folder 3)
- Hagerty, James C. (1909 -); Govt. official (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Hale, Robert F. (1909 -); Fgn. service officer (Box 15, Folder 12, Box 19, Folder 24, Box 20, Folder 4, Folder 5)
- HALF MOON BAY SEWER LINE, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Halleck, Charles A. (1900 -); Cong., 2nd Ind. (Box 5, Folder 27, Box 12, Folder 31, Box 13, Folder 6, Folder 7)
- Hamilton, Lee H. () (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Hand, T. Millet () (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Hanley, James M. () (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Hannell, A. L. () (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Hansen, George V. () (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Harden, Cecil M. (1894 -); Cong., 5th Ind. (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Harder, C. Wilson (1897 -); Organization exec. (Box 22, Folder 9, Folder 10)
- Harding, Robert W. () (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Hardy, Peter Jr. (1903 -); Cong., 2nd Va. (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Harford, James J. (1924 -); Association exec. (Box 18, Folder 29)
- Harlow, Bryce N. (1916 -); Govt. official (Box 14, Folder 31, Box 15, Folder 2, Folder 3, Box 22, Folder 15)
- Harper, Joseph H. (1901 -); Army officer (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Harrington, Julian F. (1901 -); U. S. ambassador (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Harris, Oren (1903 -); Cong., 4th Ark. (Box 10, Folder 10)
- HARRISON, FRANK, 1963 - 1966 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Hartford, T. J. (1901 -); Army med. officer (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Hauge, Gabriel (1914 -); Trust Co. exec. (Box 2, Folder 3, Folder 4, Box 11, Folder 11)
- Hawaii Statehood (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Haworth, Leland J. (1904 -); Physicist (Box 9, Folder 17, Box 11, Folder 6)
- Hays, Brooks (1898 -); Cong., 5th Ark. (Box 19, Folder 24, Box 20, Folder 5)
- Heacock, Roger Lee (1906 -); Fgn. service officer (Box 20, Folder 3)
- HEALTH, ED. & WELFARE, CORRESPONDENCE
  - 1955 - 1956 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - 1957 - 1958 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - 1959 - 1966 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- HEALTH, ED. & WELFARE, GENERAL FILE
  - 1963 - 1964 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - 1965 - 1966 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Heaman, W. M. () (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Heaton, Leonard D. (1902 -); Surgeon, Army officer (Box 2, Folder 11, Box 9, Folder 9)
- Hebert, F. Edward (1901 -); Cong., 1st La. (Box 22, Folder 24)
- Hector, Louis J. (1915 -); Govt. officer (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Henderson, John E. (1917 -); Gong., 15th Ohio (Box 15, Folder 12, Box 20, Folder 1)
- Henderson, Joseph S. (1914 -); Govt. official (Box 4, Folder 3, Folder 4, Box 5, Folder 2, Box 20)
- Henry, E. William () (Box 7, Folder 30, Folder 32)
- Hershey, Lewis B. (1893 -); Army officer (Box 18, Folder 24, Folder 25)
- Hicks, Floyd V. () (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Hiestand, Edgar W. (1888 -); Cong., 21st Cal. (Box 4, Folder 17)
- HIGHWAYS, GENERAL 1963 - 1966 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Higley, H. V. (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Hildreth, Elon E. () (Box 9, Folder 2, Box 19, Folder 25)
- Hill, Hayward G. (1900 -); Fgn. service officer (Box 20, Folder 1, Folder 4)
- Hill, Matthew W. (1894 -); Judge (Box 22, Folder 22)
- Hill, Robert C. (1917 -); Ambassador (Box 3, Folder 13, Box 6, Folder 18, Box 19, Folder 22)
- Hill, William S. () (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Hillings, Patrick J. () (Box 6, Folder 7, Box 15, Folder 12)
- Hines, W. T. (1907 -); Naval officer (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Hirshfield, J. A. () (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Hitch, Charles J. (1910 -); Economist (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Hoff, Marjorie E. (Private bill) (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Hobby, Oveta Culp (1905 -); Govt. official, Newspaper publisher (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Hoegh, Leo A. (1908 -); Govt. official (Box 2 2, Folder 15)
- Hoeven, Charles B. (1895 -); Cong., 8th Iowa (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Hoever, J. Edgar (1895 -); Director, FBI (Box 21, Folder 41, Box 12, Folder 18)
- Hoffman, Clare E. (1875 -); Cong. (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Hoffman, Richard W. () (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Holloman, John Herbert (1919 -); Metallurgist (Box 12, Folder 35)
- Holloway, James L. Jr. (1898 -); Naval officer (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Holmes, Julius C. (1899 -); U. S. Ambassador (Box 5, Folder 2, Box 20, Folder 4)
- Holt, Joe (1909 -); Fgn. Service officer (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Holtzer, Rudolf (Private bill) (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Holum, Kenneth (1915 -); Govt. official (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Home Loan Bank Act (Amendment) (Box 4, Folder 15)
- HOME LOAN BANK BOARD, GENERAL
  - 1955 - 1956 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - 1957 - 1958 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- HOME LOAN BANK BOARD, REORGANIZATION PLAN II (Box 11, Folder 13)
- HOOVER COMMISSION (ON ORG. OF GOVT.'S EXEC. BRANCH) (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Hoover, Herbert Jr. (1903 -); Consulting engineer (Box 2, Folder 3, Box 19, Folder 20, Box 20, Folder 6)
- Hope, Clifford R. (1893 -); Cong., 5th & 7th Kan. (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Hopkins, Frank S. (1908 -); Fgn. service officer (Box 19, Folder 25)
- Hopwood, Herbert G. (1898 -); Naval officer (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Horne, John E. (1908 -); Govt. official (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Hornung, L. W. (1898 -); Railroad exec. (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Hosmer, Craig (1915 -); Cong., 18th Cal. (Box 8, Folder 21, Box 13, Folder 29, Box 15, Folder 14, Box 22, Folder 28)
- HOSPITALS, 1963 - 1966 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- HOUSE BREAKFAST GROUP & SUNSET CLUB, 1955 - 1956 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- HOUSING
  - Foster City (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - 1965 - 1966 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - 1963 - 1964 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Misc. (Box 9, Folder 30, Folder 31)
- HOUSING & HOME FINANCE AGENCY, 1957 - 1962 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Howard, Leland (1907 -); Govt. official (Box 20, Folder 28)
- Hruska, Roman Lee (1904 -); U. S. Senator, Neb. (Box 2, Folder 1, Box 15, Folder 7)
- Hsu, Jen (Private bill) (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Hughes, Morris N. (1901 -); Fgn. service officer (Box 20, Folder 1, Folder 5)
- Humphrey, Hubert Horatio, Jr. (1911 -); U. S. Sen. (Box 15, Folder 3, Folder 9)
- Hunt, Herold C. (1902 -); Educator (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Hyde, DeWitt S. () (Box 3, Folder 28, Box 15, Folder 12)
- IMMIGRATION
  - 1955 - 1956 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - 1963 - 1965 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- IMMIGRATION & NATURALIZATION SERVICE, 1961 - 1963 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- IMPORTS
  - 1963 - 1964 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - 1965 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- INAUGURAL
  - 1961 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - 1965 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Income tax (Box 20, Folder 22)
- INDIAN AFFAIRS
  - 1963 - 1964 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - 1965 (Box 11, Folder 30)
- INFLATION
  - 1959 - 1960 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Misc. (Box 5, Folder 27, Folder 28)
- Institute for Defense Analysis (IDA) (Box 9, Folder 11)
- INSURANCE, GENERAL, 1963 - 1966 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- INSURANCE SECURITIES TRUST FUND, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- INTERIOR, DEPT. OF
  - 1957 - 1958 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - 1961 - 1962 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - 1963 - 1966 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Bureau of Indian affairs (Box 11, Folder 29, Folder 30)
- INTERNAL REVENUE SERVICE
  - 1955 - 1956 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - 1957 - 1958 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - 1961 - 1962 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - 1963 - 1964 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - 1965 - 1966 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- I. R. S. CASE, SCOTT (Box 12, Folder 11)
- INTERNATION AFFAIRS SEMINARS (Box 12, Folder 12)
- INTERNATIONAL COOPERATION ADMINISTRATION, 1957 - 1958 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- INTERSTATE COMMERCE CONTROL
  - 1957 - 1964 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - 1965 - 1966 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- INTRODUCTION, LETTERS OF, 1963 - 1966 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- INVITATIONS, DECLINED, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Isern, A. Fernos () (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Jack, Robert L. () (Box 12, Folder 6, Folder 7)
- Jackson, Donald L. (1910 -); Cong., 16th Cal. (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Jacobs, J. E. (1906 -); Steel co. exec. (Box 20, Folder 1)
- James, Benjamin F. (1897 -); Editor, author (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Jarman, John (1915 -); Cong., 5th Okla. (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Jenkins, Thomas A. () (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Jensen, Ben F. (1892 -); Cong., 7th Iowa (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Jernegan, John D. (1911 -); Fgn. service officer (Box 19, Folder 27)
- Johnson, Harold T. (); Cong., 2nd Cal. (Box 6, Folder 10, Folder 11, Box 13, Folder 23, Box 22, Folder 16)
- Johnson, Lester D. (1901 -); Cong., 9th Wis. (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Johnson, Nicholas () (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Johnson, Walter S. (1884 -); Lumber co. exec. (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Johnston, Olin D. (1896 -); Senator (Box 3, Folder 16, Box 7, Folder 6)
- Jonas, Charles Raper (1904 -); Cong., 10th N. C. (Box 15, Folder 6, Folder 8, Folder 12)
- Jones, C. B. () (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Jones, Judson C. (1904 -); Fgn. service officer (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Jones, Roger W. (1908 -); Govt. official (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Jordan, Frank M. () (Box 5, Folder 38, Box 15, Folder 19)
- Judd. Walter H. (1898 -); Cong., 5th Minn. (Box 13, Folder 7, Box 15, Folder 12)
- JUSTICE, DEPT. OF
  - 1957 - 1958 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - 1959 - 1960 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - 1961 - 1966 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Misc. (Box 9, Folder 29)
- JUVENILE DELINQUENCY, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Kaiser, Edgar F. (1897 -); Mfg. exec. (Box 10, Folder 16)
- KAISER, LELAND ()
  - 1957 - 1958 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Misc. (Box 11, Folder 1, Box 15, Folder 8, Folder 9, Folder 10)
- Kean, Robert W. () (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Kearney, B. W. () (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Kearns, Carroll D. (1900 -); Cong., 24th & 28th Pa. (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Keating, Kenneth B. (1900 -); Senator, N. Y. (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Keck, G. E. (1895 -); Architect (Box 22, Folder 28)
- Kelly, Joseph W. (1910 -); Army officer (Box 1, Folder 13, Folder 14, Folder 17, Folder 18, Folder 20, Folder 21, Box 9, Folder 7)
- Kelly, Ralph (1888 -); Comm. of customs (Box 20, Folder 28, Folder 29, Folder 30)
- Kelly, Robert N. () (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Kendally, David W. (1903 -); Govt. official (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Kennedy, Donald D. (1900 -); Govt. official (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Kennedy, John Fitzgerald (1917 - 1963), assasination of (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Kerr, Clark (1911 -); Univ. president (Box 5, Folder 32, Box 9, Folder 18, Box 16, Folder 8, Box 22, Folder 26, Folder 28)
- Kidwell, James B. () (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Killea, John F. () (Box 20, Folder 6)